Pedro Antonio Ramos Guardiola

Front-end Web Developer Multimedia Engineer

+34 664 658 760

- □ pedrorxmosdev@gmail.com
- pedrorxmos.com
- in linkedin.com/in/pedroramosguardiola
- github.com/pedrorxmos

about me

I am a multimedia engineer specialized in front-end web development. I stand out for my efficiency, creativity, self-learning and commitment to find innovative solutions, and I am able to work well in a team. Not only that, but I like to take on new challenges, and I am committed to keep learning and growing professionally.

habilidades

Programming languages

HTML, CSS/Scss, JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, PHP, Python, Java, ISML

Frameworks and libraries

Angular2, React, Bootstrap, Node, jQuery, Webpack

Tools and platforms

Webpack, Git, GitHub, VSCode, Wordpress, MySQL, Salesforce (Bussines & Marketing Cloud), Heroku

Soft Skills

Teamwork, creativity, commitment, productivity, learning ability, flexibility

Languages

Spanish, English B2 (Score 176 Cambrdige)

licences and certificates

First B2 (Grade B - Score 176)

Cambridge English 03/2023

· Verification: C1429611

Modern JavaScript: Guide to master the language

Udemy 09/2022

 https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UCd89356b3-0631-4ef6-88e0-0b7998421f2f/

professional experience

Front-end Web Developer (Internship)

Capgemini España S.L. 06/2022 - 08/2022

- Collaborate in the development of web components for Salesforce Commerce Cloud, which allowed me to apply my theoretical knowledge in a real working environment.
- Acquire experience in the use of tools such as Salesforce Business Manager, HTML, JS, CSS, SCSS and Bootstrap for the development of high quality web components and the improvement of the product's functionality.
- Learning from the professionals in the development team, who provided guidance and support in problem-solving and technical skills' development.

Web Developer (Internship)

Capgemini España S.L. 02/2022 - 04/2022

- · Develop web components for Salesforce Marketing Cloud.
- Use tools such as ISML, JS, JS Server-Side, CSS, Marketing Cloud and Heroku to create high quality web components and improve product functionality
- Learning from the professionals in the development team, who provided guidance and support in problem-solving and technical skills' development.

education

Postgraduate degree specializing in UX/UI, Digital Marketing and Front-end Web Development

ESAT - Escuela Superior de Arte y Tecnología 10/2022 - present

Degree in Multimedia Engineering

UV - Universitat de València. 09/2018 - 09/2022

 Outstanding grade (10) in Final Degree Project (TFG): Web application for the support and awareness of Gender Equality and Reduction of Inequality

projects

Eyecon Beauty

Eyecon Beauty is a PHP, WordPress and WooCommerce-based makeup ecommerce. Specializing in reusable and customizable eyeshadow palettes, it offers a seamless shopping experience with user accounts, bag functionality, and secure checkout. This was a project for the postgraduate in frontend web development, UX/UI and marketing digital, where I were asked to create the website for a product or service.

IGRD Resources

Final Degree Project (TFG) titled 'Web application for the support and awareness of Gender Equality and Reduction of Inequality' in collaboration with the professorship of Gamification and Open Government of the University of Valencia and the City Council of Valencia.

Weather App

Web application created from API and React that shows the current weather and the forecast for the next 5 days. It is part of the devChallenges of the front-end branch.